(Sheldon:)Thank you for driving me to work.
You know this is my day off, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Oh, good,
I'm not keeping you from anything.
- Your check-engine light is on.
- Mm-hm.
(Sheldon:)Typically that's an indicator to,
you know, check your engine.
(Penny:)It's fine. It's been on for like a month.
(Sheldon:)Well, actually, that would be all the more
reason to, you know, check your engine.
- Sheldon, it's fine.
- If it were fine, the light wouldn't be on.
(Sheldon:)That's why the manufacturer installed
that light, to let you know it's not fine.
(Penny:)Maybe the light's broken.
(Sheldon:)Is there
a check-the-check-engine-light light?
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)Studies have shown that performing tasks
such as eating, talking on a phone...
(Sheldon:)...or drinking coffee while driving
reduces one's reaction time...
(Sheldon:)...by the same factor
as an ounce of alcohol.
- Do you have any alcohol?
- Of course not.